sweetiesfreebies.com 2011-06-06

# About : Sweeties Freebies

You are here: [Home](http://sweetiesfreebies.com/) / About

Sweeties Freebies is the latest site in the Sweeties brand of sites. Wendy Limauge, aka Sweetie, has created a place where visitors can find the hottest freebies, coupons, and shopping deals to help readers save money. Her popular site, [Sweeties Sweeps](http://www.sweetiessweeps.com/), helps readers “win what they can’t afford” and her site [Sweeties Reviews](http://www.sweetiesreviews.com/) introduces readers to brands and campaigns to get involved with.

  * Sweeties Freebies is located at [www.sweetiesfreebies.com](http://www.sweetiesfreebies.com/)
  * Email: [sweetiesfreebies@gmail.com](mailto:sweetiesfreebies@gmail.com)
  * Twitter: [www.twitter.com/sweetiessweeps](http://www.twitter.com/sweetiessweeps)
  * Facebook: [www.facebook.com/sweetiesfreebies](http://www.facebook.com/sweetiesfreebies)

“Why buy it when you can get it for free”? We have heard that many times and in this economy we all looking for a little something extra. Companies want to give you a free sample, free trial, and sometimes full size product so you will try what they have to offer and hopefully buy it or at least tell your friends (word of mouth marketing). When we say free we mean free. If we post free samples, free trials, or anything else that is free you can be sure it will be 100% free for you, no strings attached.

Sometimes we find great offers that do require a purchase or they are free when you pay for shipping. We like to pass these along to our readers as well. These offers will always indicate if a purchase if required so you will know they are not 100% free.

We don’t actually send you the freebies and samples you see listed on our site. We scour the web to find free stuff for you and put them all in one place on Sweeties Freebies so you don’t have to do the work of finding them.

Extreme Couponing: We don’t really agree with the whole concept but rather focus more on saving the “casual couponer” money each week through store sales and coupon matchups. There is not need for a huge stockpile to keep extra food in your house. Most of us don’t have 30 or more hours to spend getting all of the groceries we buy for free but we can all spend a little time each week to save money on our grocery bill.

We post freebies for the United States and Canada.

**Disclaimer:** All of the freebies you see listed on this are legit offers but you should always read the information carefully on the site we are referring you to if you are unsure of giving out your information. You should always be careful when giving out your personal information online. You may want to consider signing up for a separate email just for requesting freebies or entering sweepstakes you find on the Web. We are not responsible for what is posted on the sites we list, only what is listed on our site. We CANNOT be held responsible for contents on those sites because we are not connected to them in anyway. We try to give accurate information and if there is something posted incorrectly we will gladly change it. Just contact through the form below.

**Have a freebie you found that you want us to add to the site?** Just fill out the form below.

## **Privacy Policy**

**Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Sweeties Freebies has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting Sweeties Freebies, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Sweeties Freebies then you may contact us at sweetiesfreebies@gmail.com

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

The ads you see on Sweeties Freebies are affiliate accounts for products that may be of interested to readers of this site. We may receive products or monetary compensation for recommendations made in reference to the products/ services on this website. Most ads posted are typically chosen because it’s a product we have tried and approve of.

This disclosure is made in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission’s 16 CFR, Part 255: “Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising.”

Last updated May 30, 2011
